https://www.campnashoba.com/contact-us/site-policy/

Site Policy:
Camp Nashoba® North is a registered trademark. All rights reserved.
GDPR Compliance
In line with the European General Data Protection Regulations, this is our GDPR statement which helps you to understand clearly who we are and how we use and protect any information that you give us when you use this website or contact us by another means.
Camp Nashoba is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and that there is transparency with regard to the processing of your information. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this statement.
WHAT WE COLLECT
Your personal details, which will probably include your name and your contact details and may include the names and ages of your children as submitted via email or the ‘request a brochure’ or ‘join our mailing list’ buttons on the website or on our camper registration form or website enquiry form.
WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER
Camp Nashoba will collect and hold your data for the purpose of delivering services and information to you that you have requested and to correspond with you about our camp. [Your data is stored and managed in our secure servers or the secure servers of CampMinder LLC, which is located in Boulder, Colorado, USA and is GDPR-compliant.]
If you have requested information from Camp Nashoba,registered as an alumni, orsubmitted a completed registration form to us with payment for a summer camp we will include you on our mailing list for our regular newsletter and occasional news of Camp Nashoba promotions and offers. You can opt out of this communication permanently at any time.The information we collect is only used for these purposes and only kept for so long as is
necessary to achieve these purposes. We will never pass your information to any party outside of Camp Nashoba unless required by law to do so. We will never give, sell or lease your personal information to anyone outside of Camp Nashoba.
SECURITY
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. [Our data handler, CampMinder LLC has also assured us of their GDPR compliance.]
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our website may contain links to other websites. However, once you have used a link to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
WHAT ARE COOKIES
A cookie is a small encrypted text file stored on your web browser from websites.
They are widely used by online businesses to collect data to learn more about their visitors in general. Some of the data collected includes origins of web traffic, amount of visitors and a visitors’ operating systems and browser types. Camp Nashoba may employ the use of online services which use cookies. You can disable the use of cookies in your browser
settings.
DATA PROTECTION AND REMOVAL OF DATA
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you or your child. If you would like a copy of the information we keep on our systems about you and your child please write to the Camp Nashoba office at the above address. If you believe that any
information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. You can ask us at any time to delete the information we hold on you or your child by emailing info@campnashoba.com or by calling 1-978-486-8236 or by writing to our office.
CHILD SAFETY
The safety of children is very important to us. We comply with the “Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act”. When a child under age 13 attempts to register with us, we ask that they have a parent or guardian register on their behalf. This is to ensure that the parent or guardian consents to the use of personally identifying information from that child.
If a parent wishes to refuse to permit further collection or use of their child’s information, that parent can send an email to us to request deletion of their child’s account.
Under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, no web site operator is permitted to require a child under the age of 13 to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity as a condition of participation. We abide by this requirement.
We do not share personally identifying information about users who are under the age of 13 with business partners or other third parties.
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online – for example through email, or in chat areas – that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.
Any questions about this policy statement may be emailed to Info@CampNashoba.com or you may write to us at our head office, once again using the address at the bottom of each page.
Schedule A Call
Name*
First
Last
Email*
Phone*Best Day(s) to CallBest Time(s) to CallNotesPhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
×
Find Nash! Play the Nash Scavenger Hunt
Nash the Moose has left clues that will unlock a special message (and a download)! Find Nash throughout the Camp Nashoba North site. Each time you do, he’ll reveal two letters. Collect them all to discover the message!
Download the Nash Clue Discovery Sheet to help you keep track of the letters you find, and reveal the message.
Here are two letters:
K   C
Once you’ve collected all 12 letters, unscramble them to discover Nash’s message. Click here to enter the phrase and get a free download!
×
Find Nash! Play the Nash Scavenger Hunt
Nash the Moose has left clues that will unlock a special message (and a download)! Find Nash throughout the Camp Nashoba North site. Each time you do, he’ll reveal two letters. Collect them all to discover the message!
Download the Nash Clue Discovery Sheet to help you keep track of the letters you find, and reveal the message.
Here are two letters:
E   L
Once you’ve collected all 12 letters, unscramble them to discover Nash’s message. Click here to enter the phrase and get a free download!
×
Find Nash! Play the Nash Scavenger Hunt
Nash the Moose has left clues that will unlock a special message (and a download)! Find Nash throughout the Camp Nashoba North site. Each time you do, he’ll reveal two letters. Collect them all to discover the message!
Download the Nash Clue Discovery Sheet to help you keep track of the letters you find, and reveal the message.
Here are two letters:
C   E
Once you’ve collected all 12 letters, unscramble them to discover Nash’s message. Click here to enter the phrase and get a free download!
×
Find Nash! Play the Nash Scavenger Hunt
Nash the Moose has left clues that will unlock a special message (and a download)! Find Nash throughout the Camp Nashoba North site. Each time you do, he’ll reveal two letters. Collect them all to discover the message!
Download the Nash Clue Discovery Sheet to help you keep track of the letters you find, and reveal the message.
Here are two letters:
S   E
Once you’ve collected all 12 letters, unscramble them to discover Nash’s message. Click here to enter the phrase and get a free download!
×
Find Nash! Play the Nash Scavenger Hunt
Nash the Moose has left clues that will unlock a special message (and a download)! Find Nash throughout the Camp Nashoba North site. Each time you do, he’ll reveal two letters. Collect them all to discover the message!
Download the Nash Clue Discovery Sheet to help you keep track of the letters you find, and reveal the message.
Here are your first two letters:
R   T
Once you’ve collected all 12 letters, unscramble them to discover Nash’s message. Click here to enter the phrase and get a free download!
×
Find Nash! Play the Nash Scavenger Hunt
Nash the Moose has left clues that will unlock a special message (and a download)! Find Nash throughout the Camp Nashoba North site. Each time you do, he’ll reveal two letters. Collect them all to discover the message!
Download the Nash Clue Discovery Sheet to help you keep track of the letters you find, and reveal the message.
Here are two letters:
N   A
Once you’ve collected all 12 letters, unscramble them to discover Nash’s message. Click here to enter the phrase and get a free download!
×
